In this video we are going to be using disk management to format a disk.
So here you can see I have several disk.
For example I have this disk too.
So let me create, let me just create a simple volume in this disk.
I am going to use the whole disk space.
And let me just use the letter E and then let me just call this software.
So here you can see we have a quick format.
So let me do that for the fall.
We can't really perform a quick format.
So by just clicking finish you can see it is going to actually format a disk.
But we see how the option to right click.
And here you can see we can actually format.
So what happens is the following.
If I go to my, let me just open my E drive.
Here you can see that that is how I drive.
So I want to click, let me just click to folder in this.
You can see we have a folder.
So if I decide to, I totally format my drive at this moment.
You can see we have different options.
It says the first system is the RF-S.
We can use the NTFS or Futter2.
And our location units are totally the fourth box.
We can use the four, zero, nine, six, or six, four.
Okay.
So we're going to perform a quick format and let me just click okay.
I see it's from what it is, well, we erase all data.
I'm going to say yes.
So if we go back to our volume, that's one where you can see that it's now empty.
So what we just created, for that we just created has been deleted from this folder, from this drive.
So that's how you use it this moment.
So I totally format your drive.
But at the same time if I go to my drive itself and here I can, I totally click.
You can see we also have the option of totally format.
And here we can see all the different options we have.
And I can just click that to totally format my drive.
You can see it has been formatted.